Gardens of the Night is a crime, drama film directed by Damian Harris.
After being abducted as children, and suffering years of abuse, a
teenage boy and girl find themselves living on the street.
Leslie, played by Gillian Jacobs.
Michael, played by John Malkovich.
Young Leslie, played by Ryan Simpkins.
Alex, played by Tom Arnold.
Frank, played by Kevin Zegers.
Young Donnie, played by Jermaine Scooter Smith.
Gardens of the Night is a 2008 American drama film, written and directed by Damian Harris
and starring Gillian Jacobs, John Malkovich, Ryan Simpkins, and Tom Arnold.
The film explores themes of california, cop, shelter, beating, prostitution.
The tone is emotional.